Finding aid for the Xavier University Library Committee minutes and related documents
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections
Xavier University Library Committee minutes and related documents
1946-2011
Xavier University Archives and Special Collections Phone: 513-745-4821 http://www.xavier.edu/cm/archives
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio). Library Committee
.8 linear feet (2 boxes)
Minutes of meetings and related documents of the Xavier University Library Committee.
XUA-23
History of Xavier University Library Committee
The committee has existed since at least 1946. It reviews and recommends policies and practices in the University Library.
This committee has served since at least 1946. The description of its responsibilities has changed over the years. It's charge as found in the Annual List of University Committees for 2010-11 was stated as the following: "The Committee: 1. Reviews and recommends new (or revisions to existing) library policies. 2. Receives and reviews periodic reports prepared by the Director of Content Management and Director of Discovery Services on its operations and makes recommendations based on these reports. 3. Advises the Director of Content Management and Director of Discovery Services on budgetary matters and 4. At the request of the Academic Vice President/Provost or the Associate Vice President of Information Resources participates in the evaluation of Library operations."
Scope and Content
Meeting minutes and related documents from the Xavier University Library Committee.
Statement of Arrangement
Materials are arranged into folders chronologically.
Separated Material
Some digitized Library Committee minutes can be found in the Xavier Archives Permanent Retention Drive.
Restrictions on Access
Restricted access. Please contact the Xavier University Archives staff.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects:
Xavier University (Cincinnati, Ohio)-- Libraries; Academic libraries--Ohio
Detailed Description of The Collection
- Library Committee minutes, 1946-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Library Committee minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Library Committee minutes, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Library Committee minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Library Committee minutes, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Library Committee minutes, 1973-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Library Committee minutes, 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Library Committee minutes, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Library Committee minutes, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Library Committee minutes, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Library Committee minutes, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Library Committee minutes, 2003-2006 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Library Committee minutes, 2006-2011 (Box 2, Folder 13)